Guide to the Doris Duke Audiovisual Collection, 1919-2012 and undated RL.10005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio, 1923-1989
  - Phonodiscs, 1934-1989; 198 items
    - The Little Angels Choir directed by Rev. Lawrence Roberts with Gertrude Hicks and Robert Logan of the First Baptist Church, Nutley, New Jersey, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0096)
    - The Little Angels Choir directed by Rev. Lawrence Roberts with Gertrude Hicks and Robert Logan of the First Baptist Church, Nutley, New Jersey, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0097)
    - Rev. Lawrence Roberts, Rev. Charles Banks, Elder Jeff Banks. Prayers for Every Occasion, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0098)
    - Rev. and Mrs. Lawrence Roberts. Presenting…, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0100)
    - DDCF Unknown 1, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0104_DDCF_Unknown_1_Gallon_01; RL10005-PD-0104_DDCF_Unknown_1_Gallon_02)
      Track 1 is Edmund Goulding narrating a story about a "boy" injured on the battle field. Others "act out" the story, including Doris Duke. Can hear people laughing the in background. Track 2 is Edmund Goulding talking about Duke Farms/Somerville as if he were advertising it as a place to stay for vacation.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0104)
    - DDCF Unknown 2, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0105_DDCF_Unknown_2_01; RL10005-PD-0105_DDCF_Unknown_2_02)
      First track begins with unknown man saying "Quiet, quiet". Then unknown person playing "The Very Thought of You" on piano. Immediately transitions into "It Had to Be You" with unknown person whistling along with piano. Track 2 is unknown man singing "Falling in Love with Love" accompanied by piano. Man transitions into unknown song, then transitions into "A Pretty Girl is Like a Melody". Doesn't sing, but hums along with piano.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0105)
    - Joe Castro Trio. It Don't Mean A Thing, Black and Blue, It's All Right With Me / Things Ain't What They Used To Be, Have You Met Miss Jones?, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0108_Joe_Castro_Trio_01; RL10005-PD-0108_Joe_Castro_Trio_02)
      Songs are instrumental only; includes piano, bass and drums. Very "jazzy" versions of songs.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0108)
    - Teddy Edwards. Angel City, Bear Tracks, Lee Ann, Midnight Creeper / Theme For Jay, Nairobi Chant, That Old Mood Again, Steppin' Lightly, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0110_Teddy_Edwards_1_01; RL10005-PD-0110_Teddy_Edwards_1_02)
      Songs are instrumental only. Teddy Edwards on tenor sax and Joe Castro on piano? Also includes drums, bass, and horns.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0110)
    - Teddy Edwards. Angel City, Bear Tracks, Lee Ann, Midnight Creeper / Theme For Jay, Nairobi Chant, That Old Mood Again, Steppin' Lightly, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0111_Teddy_Edwards_2_01; RL10005-PD-0111_Teddy_Edwards_2_02)
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0111)
    - Ginger Holiday. Brazilian Blues / Happy Blues, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0114_Brazilian_Happy_Blues_01; RL10005-PD-0114_Brazilian_Happy_Blues_02)
      Track one is instrumental only. Presumably Ginger Holiday playing "Brazilian Blues" on piano. Track two is also piano instrumental, presumably Ginger Holiday playing "Happy Blues".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 19, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0114)
    - Libby Holman. The Party's Over / Besoin De Vous, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0115)
    - Narration, Men and Money, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0119)
    - Ramona. "Blue Skies," with Ray Bloch's Orchestra / "These Foolish Things," with Schaeffer Orchestra and Chorus, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0120)
    - Unknown. Goin' To The Dance / "Monkey See, Monkey Do", undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0122_Goin_Dance_Monkey_See_01; RL10005-PD-0122_Goin_Dance_Monkey_See_02)
      Side 1 is unknown singer with backup band/singers singing "Goin' to the Dance." Side two is same singers singing "Monkey See, Monkey Do".Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0122)
    - Unknown. Outskirts of Town, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0123_Outskirts_of_Town_01)
      Ray Charles(?) singing "Outskirts of Town" accompanied by piano and saxophone.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0123)
    - Unknown. Tell Me Now / Island of Romance, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0004, Audio-file RL10005-PD-0124_Tell_Me_Now_Island_Romance_01; RL10005-PD-0124_Tell_Me_Now_Island_Romance_02)
      Unknown singer singing "Tell Me Now" and "Island of Romance". Accompanied by orchestra.Digital use copy is available in the Reading Room
      - Phonodisc (Box 20, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0124)
    - Fats Waller. Playing, Singing, and Talking In Previously Unreleased Performances - Sides 1 and 4, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0136)
    - Fats Waller. Playing, Singing, and Talking In Previously Unreleased Performances - Sides 2 and 3, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0137)
    - Kitty White. Do It Again/Visit Me, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0138)
    - Kitty White. Do It Again/Visit Me, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0139)
    - Rev. Lawrence Roberts. What Makes A Man Turn His Back On God/Dreams Can Come True, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0143)
    - Unknown ( record title and artist is written in Russian), undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0144)
    - Cissy Houston. I Love You/Making Love, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0145)
    - Gospel Harmonettes. You've Been Good To Me/Step by Step, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0146)
    - Various artists. Island in the Sun, Every Time I Pass/Banana Boat, Shame and Scandal in the Family, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 21, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0149)
    - Unknown. Goin' To The Dance, Tell Me Now, Island Of Romance, Monkey See, Monkey Do, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0162)
    - Kitty White. Untitled, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0163)
    - Kitty White. Untitled, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0164)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0165)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0166)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0167)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0168)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0169)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0170)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0171)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0172)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0173)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0174)
    - Doris (Duke?). Divali / Same?, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0175)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0176)
    - France Up?/Ruthie, undated
      - Original lacquer phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0177)
    - Big and The Evolution. Thou Shalt Not Kill/Hate's Growing Stronger, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0178)
    - Big and The Evolution. Thou Shalt Not Kill/Hate's Growing Stronger, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0179)
    - Café de Chinitas. Felices Pascuas Y Feliz Ano Nuevo, undated
      - Phonodisc (Box 22, Audio-phonodisc RL10005-PD-0181)
  - Open reel audio tapes, 1950-1970; 128 items
    - King Cole at the Piano, Capitol Records H-156, circa 1950 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001004001.wav)
      Includes 8 songs: Poor Butterfly, Blues in My Shower, Cole Capers, These Foolish Things, How High the Moon, Moonlight in Vermont, I'll Never Be the Same, and Three Little Words
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0004)
    - Art Simmons at the Living Room - Paris, 1964 October 29 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001037001.wav;ddr001037002.wav)
      Includes songs Stop Look and Listen, Our Love is Here to Stay, How About You, Jubilation, How High the Moon, Bag's Groove, Walking Shoes, We'll Be Together Again, Rat Race, After Hours
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0037)
    - Maurice Rocco, Bamboo Bar, Oriental Hotel, Bangkok Thailand, [1965 January 30] (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001034001.wav)
      Includes songs Don't Worry About Me, A Train, Basin Street, But Not For Me, Nice Work If You Can Get It
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0034)
    - Maurice Rocco, Bamboo Bar, Oriental Hotel, Bangkok Thailand, 1965 January 30 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001025001.wav)
      Includes songs Them There Eyes, San Francisco, Just in Time, and Darktown Strutter's Ball
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0025)
    - Maurice Rocco, Bamboo Bar, Oriental Hotel, Bangkok Thailand, [1965 January 30] (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001028001.wav)
      Includes songs Workin' on a String, Learnin' the Blues, P.S. I Love You, Pennies from Heaven, Lover
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0028)
    - Maurice Rocco, Bamboo Bar, Oriental Hotel, Bangkok Thailand, 1965 January 30 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001030001.wav)
      Includes songs When You're Smiling, On the Street Where You Live, Blue Moon, I Love Paris, ?, Never on Sunday, Am I Blue, ?
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0030)
    - Rl 32, 1965 August 18 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001111001.wav)
      Group 3 Tiva Tahaa Island (2 songs); Group 4 Tevaitoa Raiatea Island (3 songs); Group 5 Utoroa City Raiaea Island (1 song); Group 6 Taupoomu Tahaa Island (3 songs); Group 7 Vaitoaqe Tahaa Island (1 song); Group 8 Opoa Raiaea Island (2 songs)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0111)
    - Jodo Inc. (Kitty White) (Clover Records), 1966 January 5 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001072001.wav)
      Includes songs Honeysuckle Rose, Call Me Darlin', Happiness is a Thing Called Joe, Chance to Love You, Just in Time, Disenchanted Lady, Summer in the City
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0072)
    - Kitty White Background Tracks, 1966 January 14 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001078001.wav)
      Includes songs Say It Isn't So, My Kind of Guy, So Many Beautiful Men, Honeysuckle Rose, Call Me Darlin', Happiness is a Thing Called Joe, Oh! For Just a Chance to Love You, Just In Time, Do It Again, Dis-Enchanted Lady, Visit Me, Mood Indigo, Summer in the City
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0078)
    - Clover Records - Kitty White, 1966 February 11 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001079001.wav)
      Two sides. First side includes songs Visit Me, Summer in the City, My Kind of Guy, Happiness is a Thing Called Joe, So Many Beautiful Men, Do It Again, Call Me Darling. Second side includes songs Disenchanted Lady, Oh, For Just a Chance to Love You, Say It Isn't So, Just In Time, Mood Indigo
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0079)
    - Rough Dub Down 4 Track to Mono, Clover Records, Joe Castro Session, 1966 May 27 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001071001.wav)
      Includes songs Sweet Pea, Sunset Eyes, Funky Blues, Hard to Find, Play Me the Blues, and For Carl
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0071)
    - Reels 11 & 12, 1967 July (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001110001.wav)
      Track 11 includes underwater sounds, person swimming, fishes petting mike, water sounds. Track 12 includes sea bird, atmosphere in wood, slight breeze, insects and wind in coconut palms - all recorded at Moorea.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0110)
    - Reels 25 & 26, 1967 July (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001108001.wav)
      Track 25 includes spear throwing sounds, girls at waterfall, outrigger sounds, gull birds, surf from outrigger, walking outrigger through water. Track 26 includes island, water, wind in trees, splitting coconut out of husk, chicks.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0108)
    - Reels 27 & 28, 1967 July (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001106001.wav)
      Includes Hotel musicians, walking through fete
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0106)
    - Reels 27 & 28?. Could also be reel 33 (as marked on box), circa 1967
      Back cover has been covered with label. Rl 33 written on back cover, however 27 & 28 written in marker on reel.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0116)
    - Rl 29, 1967 July 16 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001112001.wav)
      Rhythm Group in Bora Bora. Includes Ave Tuna Tuna, Vaitiporo, Kani Kani, No'o (male group)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0112)
    - Tiare Tahiti (Paulina0; Te Maeva; Tahiti Fete, 1967 July 20 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001104001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0104)
    - RL 33, 1967 July 20 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001107001.wav)
      Te Maeva, Tefana (FAAA) District, Tahiti Fete
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0107)
    - RL 35, 1967 July 20 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001113001.wav)
      Includes male group mic moves during dance giving trouble throughout, Tahiti Fete.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0113)
    - RL 36, 1967 July 20 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001114001.wav)
      Includes Tiare; Tahiti Fete.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0114)
    - Rl 43 Tahiti Hotel, 1967 July 21 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001105001.wav)
      Recorded at Hotel Tahiti; singing and dancing coverage caused usual problems in public show. Background of crickets, cars, people, boats, surf.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0105)
    - Tahiti - Tahiti Hotel Group, 1967 July 21 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001109001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0109)
    - Stuart, Arden - Orc. Reh, 1967 October 23 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001080001.wav)
      Includes songs Goody Goody, Misty Roses, Rock Medley, Gone Medley, I Love Jazz, It All Depends on You, Autumn Leaves, Mellow Tone, Like A Woman, You Do Something To Me, Unchain My Heart, Let's Do It
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0080)
    - Syd Shaw Reel 1 & 2, circa 1967 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001102001.wav)
      ? Grounds in the evening, surf in the background, occasional cars crickets; Bird sounds - Budgies and Pidgeons, Budgies fighting. Also includes taking off and landing.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0102)
    - Tahiti Rl 20, circa 1967 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001103001.wav)
      Also includes "Me Goofing" handwritten by Doris Duke on back cover.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0103)
    - Tahiti, circa 1967 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001118001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0118)
    - Reel 32, circa 1967 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001122001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0122)
    - RL 25 Tahiti, circa 1967 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001123001.wav)
      Includes male talking, spear throwing sounds, girls at waterfall, wash of stag? of outrigger, bird gull type, surf from outrigger, walking outrigger thro water and coral reefs
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0123)
    - Reel 25 Girls at Waterfall, circa 1967 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001124001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0124)
    - Track 8 - Tahitian Music, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001120001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0120)
    - Art Simmons, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001006001.wav)
      Includes songs How High (4 versions), Sweet Lorraine, Can't Get Started, blues in e - A
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0006)
    - Art Simmons, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001009001.wav)
      Includes songs How High, Can't Get Started
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0009)
    - Arab Dance / Aretha., undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001010001.wav)
      Includes songs Without a Word, Feel Good
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0010)
    - Sid Shaw / Andy Cummings, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001011001.wav;ddr001011002.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0011)
    - Art Simmons / Michel Gaudry?, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001012001.wav)
      Includes songs Blues Paris, Until the Real Thing Comes Along, Blues in G EAD
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0012)
    - Bernie, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001013001.wav;ddr001013002.wav)
      Includes songs It All Depends, Let's Do It, I Love Jazz, Gone Medley, Unchain My Heart (B flat), Let's Do It (1 7/8 new version)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0013)
    - Sid Shaw - Bernie Hoff? Backgrounds, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001121001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0121)
    - Doris / Art, Newport., undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001065001.wav)
      Doris Duke and Art Simmons practice session presumably at Newport, RI. Both Doris and Art play the piano. Includes songs Can't Get Started, Sweet Lorraine, Art blues, and Indiana.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0065)
    - Doris / Art, Newport., undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001125001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 46, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0125)
    - Art, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001089001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0089)
    - Artie, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001014001.wav)
      Includes Group background and 3 versions of Blues Inc.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0014)
    - Art & Practice, Newport, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001066001.wav)
      Doris Duke and Art Simmons practice session presumably at Newport, RI. Both Doris and Art play the piano. Includes songs Blues, Indiana, and Forever. Both Doris and Art periodically comment on their performances.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0066)
    - Art & Practice, Newport, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001126001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 46, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0126)
    - Art & Practice, Newport, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001127001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 46, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0127)
    - Art Simmons Paris, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001015001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0015)
    - Art at Living Room, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001021001.wav)
      Includes songs Moanin', Sweet Lorraine, Boy's Blues in F, Blues in e, Can't Get Started, and Answering Blues
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0021)
    - Kitty White, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001070001.wav)
      Supposedly a copy of Kitty White's dub. Includes 7 songs, however these have been crossed off in pencil. "Goofing" is handwritten on the front cover.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0070)
    - Kitty White - Reel I, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001073001.wav)
      Includes songs You Do Something to Me, Lush Life, Happiness is a Thing, Heart Belongs to Daddy, My Heart Skips, Honeysuckle Rose, After You've Gone, You Came a Long Way From St. Louis, Momma Done Tole Me, You Go to My Head, Honeysuckle Rose. Next to each song, Doris wrote whether song was Good or Fair.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0073)
    - Kitty White - Reel II, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001069001.wav)
      Includes songs Little Girl Blue, Lush Life, Just in Time, Mad About You (2 versions), Baby All the ?, Got the World on a String, You Made Me Love You, Swell Hotel. Next to each song Doris handwrote whether the song was Good, Fair, or No.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0069)